<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>זכרונות מהודו Off to India</title>
        <singer classification="unknown">אסי רוז</singer>
        <writer>אסי רוז</writer>
        <composer>אסי רוז</composer>
        <album>missing</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>זכרונות מהודו Off to India</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>Ladies and Germany, this is Radio India Broadcasting to you </l>
          <l>right now in International frequency </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="2" type="stanza">
          <l>Bye Bye Mom I’m of to India, Don’t worry I, will not catch Bacteria </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="3" type="stanza">
          <l>Don’t make a fuss, don’t make a mess, just relax and play your bingo </l>
          <l>I’m off to Rishikesh just like John, Paul, George and Ringo </l>
          <l>Eventually I’ll be back I will bring you a carved elephant </l>
          <l>I’ll be carrying books on my back and return much more intelligent. </l>
          <l>I’m going to Ladakh at the top of the Himalayas </l>
          <l>To meditate a lot with the Yogies &amp; The Babas </l>
          <l>If I feel I need a guru I’ll be looking for the Dalai Lama </l>
          <l>If I feel I need a guru I’ll be looking To Dharam Sala </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="4" type="stanza">
          <l>Bye Bye Mom I’m of to India, Don’t worry I, will not catch Bacteria </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="5" type="stanza">
          <l>I’ll meet a Sadhu on the Road doing Yoga like a Budha </l>
          <l>I give him some Rupy he will teach me Kama Sutra </l>
          <l>Chai in the morning sun after Kundalini Tantra </l>
          <l>I will reach Enlightenment and be spinning all my Chakra </l>
          <l>Coconut from the trees, Mango and Papaya </l>
          <l>I will be so healthy drinking Smoothy with Banana </l>
          <l>The Full Moon will rise on beach party in anjuna </l>
          <l>I'll be dancing all night with the dolphin and the Tuna </l>
          <l>Bye Bye Mom, </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="6" type="stanza">
          <l>no going Goa come to Varansai I give you riksha coffee &amp; bang lassi </l>
          <l>Ladies ‫&amp;‬ Germany come look my shop‫.‬no passing passing Madam please stop </l>
          <l>only looking no need to buy only chai and bye bye </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="7" type="stanza">
          <l>Bye Bye Mom I’m of to India, Don’t worry I, will not catch Bacteria </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="8" type="stanza">
          <l>Come to India, Indi indi India, Come to India, No Bacteria </l>
          <l>Come to my brother Hotel, everything working very very well </l>
          <l>AC conditioning perfectly clean nothing to worry no Rats to be seen </l>
          <l>Breakfast on the house, but beware of the mouse. . </l>
          <l>but its only a tiny little tiny mouse </l>
          <l>It is a very good mouse </l>
          <l>It is my friend. I call him Ganesh.</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
