<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>Migraine In Katmandu</title>
        <singer classification="unknown">אביטל רז</singer>
        <writer>אביטל רז</writer>
        <composer>אביטל רז</composer>
        <album>missing</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>Migraine In Katmandu</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>If this pit had no bottom </l>
          <l>We'd float like feathers down and down and down and down </l>
          <l>All melancholy farewell </l>
          <l>We would not need to hold on. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="2" type="stanza">
          <l>There's a boy I meet in India </l>
          <l>He's full of holes and a big tattoo on his forearm </l>
          <l>He sais that Natraj is the god of destruction for the sake of rebirth </l>
          <l>He sais he's got to go home soon, His folks think he's up to no good </l>
          <l>He plans to sell paper butterflies at festivals to people who can't fly. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="3" type="stanza">
          <l>There once was a girl who's face was all scarred up </l>
          <l>From years of trying to be perfect. </l>
          <l>She drank a magic potion that burned off those layers of skin </l>
          <l>Leaving her as fresh as a flower. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg Chorus="yes" number="4" type="stanza">
          <l>Layers and layers and layers of skin, magic potions, pits without bottoms, paper butterflies... </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="5" type="stanza">
          <l>I once knew a lady, she couldn't breathe too well </l>
          <l>She had to change houses every year or two </l>
          <l>Some people knew her as very fat and some people knew her as too skinny. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="6" type="stanza">
          <l>If I were a figure in a Chinese painting, I'd take small steps. </l>
          <l>I'd carry myself so lightly I'd float through pain </l>
          <l>I'd float through pain </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="7" type="stanza">
          <l>Some people note three times unhappy, unhappy, unhappy and try not to fall asleep. </l>
          <l>They try to stay watchful and greet whoever wanders in. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="8" type="stanza">
          <l>This night isn't dark this night is full of stars </l>
          <l>I haven't locked the gate </l>
          <l>So come night wanderers , come without wanting </l>
          <l>But, please do come without wanting </l>
          <l>wanting </l>
          <l>wanting</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>