<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>Strange Love Song</title>
        <singer classification="unknown">אביטל רז</singer>
        <writer>אביטל רז</writer>
        <composer>אביטל רז</composer>
        <album>missing</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>Strange Love Song</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>My baby- he's weak and he's nasty and once he made me stand out in the pouring rain. He's sweeter than honey, softer than a feather. His heart is like a frightened deer. </l>
          <l>He's got no education, no qualification, got no job, no money, no plans, no future. But he's got lot's of colorful pictures of Gods and Godess' and tiny plates and bells. He gives them flowers and water every day. </l>
          <l>My baby - he's weak and he's nasty. </l>
          <l>He cheated on me, he ignored me, he fucked me. He left me crying on the street corner. He drinks, he smokes, he sucks my blood and he whines in my ear like a mosquito - But he never never ever lied to me. </l>
          <l>His heart is deeper than the deepest ocean and I am the luminous creature in its depth. I am his creepy sea monster. I am his pearl. </l>
          <l>We hurt one another, hurt ourselves and each other - Our love is real - it's a bloody mess and not the bullshit of movies and people that don't have a clue about life. When I told him I was leaving, he cried so hard, his head fell back, with his mouth wide open - even his teeth were crying. I've gone away to pray all day. I'll stay away till I'm OK and then I'll fly to him on a magic bird and scoop up my beautiful baby. </l>
          <l>Then he will sing me a strange love song</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
