<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>These Words You Want To Hear</title>
        <singer classification="male singer">אסף אבידן</singer>
        <writer>אסף אבידן</writer>
        <composer>אסף אבידן</composer>
        <album>Gold Shadow</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>These Words You Want To Hear</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>Don't you think it's time you get on over that?</l>
          <l>Don't you think you had enough? I mean, I know you had it rough,</l>
          <l>But that pansy-fancy way of looking grim all through the day and night?</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="2" type="stanza">
          <l>Is something wrong my dear? Have I said it way to clear?</l>
          <l>Then let me whisper in your ear, all these words I know are wrong</l>
          <l>But for the sake of writing song - Here is what I guess you want to hear</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="3" type="stanza">
          <l>Somewhere up there, the sky is blue for you</l>
          <l>Somewhere out there, there's something new to do</l>
          <l>Somebody loves you </l>
          <l>Somebody loves you</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="4" type="stanza">
          <l>Tell me do you think you have some exclusivity </l>
          <l>On every shadow of regret that's lurking in proximity </l>
          <l>To what you think your life should be$ But if you close your eyes you’ll see</l>
          <l>That there is nothing for you here, still the only words you hear are - </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="5" type="stanza">
          <l>Somewhere up there, the sky is blue for you</l>
          <l>Somewhere out there, there's something new to do</l>
          <l>Somebody loves you</l>
          <l>Somebody loves you</l>
        </lg>
        <lg Chorus="yes" number="6" type="stanza" />
        <lg Chorus="yes" number="7" type="stanza" />
        <lg Chorus="yes" number="8" type="stanza" />
        <lg number="9" type="stanza">
          <l>Now tell me how about we maybe switch things for a change?</l>
          <l>I will lie down in denial and you can have this page</l>
          <l>It's condescending and it's sad, you're not the only one that's had </l>
          <l>A life like this, I'm sorry dear, but it’s what everybody wants to hear</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>