<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>United</title>
        <singer classification="unknown">אביש 4</singer>
        <writer>שי 360</writer>
        <composer>קיימים 3 ביצועים נוספים לשיר זה</composer>
        <album>missing</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>United</head>
        <lg Chorus="yes" number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>When the world's gone lost</l>
          <l>We're gonna help you find the way</l>
          <l>Too much drama in my eyes that I can't hide</l>
          <l>When the world's gone lost</l>
          <l>I don't plan to fall with it</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="2" type="stanza">
          <l>I'm on the wrong side of the map, activists with knifes got me trapped</l>
          <l>Surrounded by hostility, trying not to react</l>
          <l>Flotillas of hatred, we're caught in the matrix</l>
          <l>I'm trying to survive, they're pulling the same tricks</l>
          <l>This international hypocrisy won't get us far</l>
          <l>One-sided media puts us behind bars</l>
          <l>Nations with no minorities, judging with no authority</l>
          <l>They're gonna tell me how to deal with what's in front of me</l>
          <l>What about Sudan and North Korea? Could they care less?!</l>
          <l>They wanna boycott us, they're gonna share less</l>
          <l>We're lying on the fence for the rest of the world</l>
          <l>Provide a buffer zone while overseas they get us sold</l>
          <l>I know my people can be divided at times</l>
          <l>Got too many opinions with too much shit on our minds</l>
          <l>You can hate us now, we ain't gonna fight it</l>
          <l>You're only making us stronger and more united</l>
        </lg>
        <lg Chorus="yes" number="3" type="stanza">
          <l>When the world's gone lost</l>
          <l>We're gonna help you find the way</l>
          <l>Too much drama in my eyes that I can't hide</l>
          <l>When the world's gone lost</l>
          <l>I don't plan to fall with it</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="4" type="stanza">
          <l>‏But I'm already home and the media distorts your vision</l>
          <l>‏Got blind followers here in full submission</l>
          <l>‏Provocateurs,‬ they just wanna instigate</l>
          <l>‏And create the image you love to hate</l>
          <l>‏You can talk about humanitarian aid</l>
          <l>‏Politically affiliated IHH</l>
          <l>‏Guess who's more popular? Erdogan</l>
          <l>‏Fuck left and right, we should all stand as one</l>
          <l>‏You really thought we were gonna let 'em in?</l>
          <l>‏When yesterday they tried to bring Karine A</l>
          <l>Was that aid or to arm Jihad?</l>
          <l>‏Wanna talk about aid? What about Gilad?</l>
          <l>‏Because their horse is trojan, doors not open</l>
          <l>‏I gotta do whatever to protect my home and</l>
          <l>‏I'm a peace dealer, my flow killa</l>
          <l>‏But no peace came at me on the flotilla</l>
        </lg>
        <lg Chorus="yes" number="5" type="stanza">
          <l>When the world's gone lost</l>
          <l>We're gonna help you find the way</l>
          <l>Too much drama in my eyes that I can't hide</l>
          <l>When the world's gone lost</l>
          <l>I don't plan to fall with it</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>